sunnyislesmiamirealestate.com 2007-05-15

# Miami Condos & Luxury Real Estate, Mls & Preconstruction Condo

|   
   **About Us**

* * *

   **Articles & News**

* * *

   **Miami MLS Search**

* * *

   **Ft. Lauderdale MLS**

* * *

   **Sell Your Property**

* * *

   **100 Most Recent Sales**

* * *

   **100 Most Expensive**

* * *

   **Market Analysis**

* * *

   **Miami PreConstruction**

* * *

   **Foreign Investors**

* * *

   **Property Search**

* * *

   **Mortgage Center**

* * *

   **Mortgage Calculator**

* * *

   **Disclaimer**

* * *

   **Employment**

* * *

   **Your Privacy**

* * *

   **Site Map**

* * *

   **Blog Miami Condos**

* * *

   **Contact Us**

* * *

   **Newsletter**

* * *

   **Resources**  

|   
---  

---  
|  Sign up to receive our  _newsletter_. Find out about Miami real estate & MLS, preconstruction condos, latest news, articles, recent sales and more.   
  
---  
|  |  |  |   |   
Privacy Policy  
  
---|---  
  |  We are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. Your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That's why, when you visit SunnyRealtyFL.com, we help you maintain control over your data on the Internet. 

**Specific types of information we ask for**

In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate. For example, we request information from you when you: 

1\. Register on SunnyRealtyFL.com   
2\. Provide feedback in an online survey  
3\. Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer   
4\. Request e-mail notification for your questions  
6\. Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list  
7\. Request assistance 

In each of the instances above, we may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, customer preference information as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you. In the case of newsletters or mailing lists, you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time. 

**The information we collect only used for specific purposes**

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support customer relationship with SunnyRealtyFL.com. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on SunnyRealtyFL.com and alert you to special offers, updated information and other new products and services from SunnyRealtyFL.com. Agents or contractors of SunnyRealtyFL.com who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for SunnyRealtyFL.com. SunnyRealtyFL.com may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you. 

**You can opt-out of receiving further marketing from us at any time**

We will send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only SunnyRealtyFL.com (or agents working on behalf of SunnyRealtyFL.com and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of receiving further marketing from SunnyRealtyFL.com by typing "remove" in the subject of your email. SunnyRealtyFL.com will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of SunnyRealtyFL.com for the purpose of performing services for SunnyRealtyFL.com. 

**Third-Party Sites**

Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked to SunnyRealtyFL.com are not covered by this privacy statement. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, SunnyRealtyFL.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

**Other Websites**

SunnyRealtyFL.com contain links to other websites that are not operated by SunnyRealtyFL.com. SunnyRealtyFL.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the websites that it does not operate. All text in conjunction with listings in any of the Specialty Hosting sections are provided by and the intellectual property of each particular web hosting company. SunnyRealtyFL.com does not specifically endorse, favor, or promote any of the individual web host companies listed on this site. 

**Contact SunnyRealtyFL.com**

SunnyRealtyFL.com is the sole operator of the electronic web pages known as SunnyRealtyFL.com and are © Copyright 2004-2005 by SunnyRealtyFL.com. All rights reserved. If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please call, write, or email us at the following address: 

**Mailing Address:**   
SunnyRealtyFL.com.  
177 Sunny Isles Blvd.  
Sunny Isles Beach, FL 33160

 **Toll Free:**  
1-877-368-2318

**Customer Care:**  
954-336-1016

**Fax:**  
305-935-1301

**General Feedback:** [ _feedback@SunnyRealtyFL.com_](mailto:feedback@SunnyRealtyFL.com)

Effective Date: 5/15/2007   
|    
|
